MAI GOHARA

Front-end Developer

Web developer with additional experience designing advertisements for apps and websites. I worked for several Vancouver start-up companies to improve their application as a Front-end Developer. I like to learn new skills in web technology and updating my knowledge and especially good at React and UI design.

 \bigvee

maigohara-1103@outlook.jp



(604)-690-0583



Vancouver, BC



maigohara.com

SKILLS

React HTML SCSS Sketch Illustrator Lightroom After Effects

TypeScript CSS JavaScript Figma Photoshop Premiere Pro

WORK EXPERIENCE

UI / UX Designer | Internship

Omni App Lab | April 2020 - July 2020

Omni App Lab creates different types of mobile applications, including health management, international student assistance, or recruitment information apps.

- · Created app wireframes and logos
- Researched similar applications to determine common inconveniences for users, including button movement, page movement, or colours before the making the wireframe
- · Researched user-friendly designs to ensure implementation of the best UX practices
- · Created company and application logos that clearly showcase the company concept and branding

Web Designer & Photographer

Sports IT Solution, Inc. | December 2016 - April 2019

Sports IT Solution creates and operates management systems, mobile applications, and websites for sports competitions.

- Created campaign banner and event page for Japanese football league's official application
- · Wrote articles about sports for the website
- · Photographed the football team, interviews, and sports competition
- · Directed video production about Tokyo2020 with government

Server Engineer

CLARA ONLINE, Inc. | January 2016 - November 2016

Clara Online builds, operates, and maintains servers in Japan and China. Consults internet and mobile businesses in Asian countries.

· Supported customers experiencing troubles with their LINUX server

EDUCATION

Web & Mobile App Development Diploma

Cornerstone International Community College of Canada - Vancouver September 2019 - September 2020

Film & Moving Image Major

Tokyo Zokei University - Tokyo April 2010 - March 2014

VOLUNTEER WORK

Front-end Developer

VINPLE, Inc. | November 2019 - September 2020

VINPLE created a mobile and web application called BASE for collaborating and networking with students across BC.

- Modified issues and implemented new features for the web app using React, Redux, MobX, SCSS, TypeScript and React Bootstrap
- Implemented responsive version using React Bootstrap, SCSS. Improved chat page readability and responsiveness by adding a new component to move the chat page, adding a function to show the group chat name, and modifying bug affecting the chat bubble text
- · Helped other team members by explaining the purpose of the code and functions

SCHOOL PROJECT

Front-end Developer

8it Technology, Inc. | June 2020 - August 2020

8it Technology created a mobile application called PIKADISH for simplifying food decisions.

- Created Management portal for a restaurant owner with a team using React, TypeScript, firebase, Emotion, and Ant.Design as a school project
- · Considered a better way to implement the portal base design and implemented it using Ant.Design and Emotion
- · Implemented restaurant photo gallery using React library, firebase and TypeScript, and organized functions related to firebase
- · Collaborated with designer to create a user-friendly way to view and delete photos from photo gallery
- · Implemented restaurant information edit page using simple and efficient code